<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My City</string>
    <string name="list_fragment_label">Places to Visit</string>
    <string name="detail_fragment_label">Details</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>

    <string name="qutub_minar_description">The Qutb Minar, also spelled Qutub Minar and Qutab Minar, is a minaret and \"victory tower\" that forms part of the Qutb complex, which lies at the site of Delhi\'s oldest fortified city, Lal Kot, founded by the Tomar Rajputs. It consists of 399 steps [3] It is a UNESCO World Heritage Site in the Mehrauli area of South Delhi, India.[4][5] It is one of the most visited tourist spots in the city, mostly built between 1199 and 1220.</string>
    <string name="rashtrapati_bhawan_description">The Rashtrapati Bhavan (pronunciationⓘ, ISO: Rāṣṭrapati Bhavana; lit. \'Presidential Palace\'; formerly Viceroy\'s House from 1931 to 1947 and Government House from 1947 to 1950) is the official residence of the President of India at the western end of Rajpath, Raisina Hill in New Delhi. It was formerly known as Viceroy\'s House and constructed during the zenith of British Empire. Rashtrapati Bhavan may refer to only the 340-room main building that has the president\'s official residence, including reception halls, guest rooms and offices, also called the mansion; it may also refer to the entire 130-hectare (320-acre) Presidential Estate that additionally includes the presidential gardens, large open spaces, residences of bodyguards and staff, stables, other offices and utilities within its perimeter walls. In terms of area, it is the second largest residence of any head of state in the world after Quirinal Palace in Italy.[3] The other presidential homes are the Rashtrapati Nilayam in Hyderabad, Telangana and The Retreat Building in Shimla, Himachal Pradesh.\n</string>
    <string name="india_gate_description">The India Gate (formerly known as All India War Memorial) is a war memorial located near the Kartavya path on the eastern edge of the \"ceremonial axis\" of New Delhi, formerly called Rajpath in New Delhi. It stands as a memorial to 74,187 soldiers of the Indian Army who died between 1914 and 1921 in the First World War, in France, Flanders, Mesopotamia, Persia, East Africa, Gallipoli and elsewhere in the Near and the Far East, and the Third Anglo-Afghan War. 13,300 servicemen\'s names, including some soldiers and officers from the United Kingdom, are inscribed on the gate.[2] Designed by Sir Edwin Lutyens, the gate evokes the architectural style of the ancient Roman triumphal arches such as the Arch of Constantine in Rome, and later memorial arches; it is often compared to the Arc de Triomphe in Paris, and the Gateway of India in Mumbai.</string>
    <string name="red_fort_description">The Red Fort or Lal Qila (Hindustani: [laːl qiːlaː]) is a historic fort in Delhi, India, that historically served as the main residence of the Mughal emperors. Emperor Shah Jahan commissioned construction of the Red Fort on 12 May 1639, when he decided to shift his capital from Agra to Delhi. Originally red and white, its design is credited to architect Ustad Ahmad Lahori, who also constructed the Taj Mahal. The fort represents a high point in the Mughal architecture under Shah Jahan and combines Persian palace architecture with Indian traditions.</string>
    <string name="tughlakabad_fort_description">Tughluqabad Fort is a ruined fort in Delhi, India. It was constructed by Ghiyasuddin Tughluq, the founder of the Tughlaq dynasty, of the Delhi Sultanate in 1321 as he established the third historic city of Delhi, but it was later abandoned in 1327. The fort lends its name to the nearby Tughluqabad residential-commercial area as well as the Tughluqabad Institutional Area. Ghiyasuddin Tughluq also built the Qutub-Badarpur Road, which connected the new city to the Grand Trunk Road. The road is now known as Mehrauli-Badarpur Road.[1] The entry fee for the Fort is Rs. 20 for Indians.[2] Also, nearby is Dr. Karni Singh Shooting Range and Okhla Industrial Area.</string>
    <string name="hauz_khas_fort_description">Hauz Khas Complex in Hauz Khas, South Delhi houses a water tank, an Islamic seminary, a mosque, a tomb, and pavilions built around an urbanized village with medieval history traced to the 13th century of Delhi Sultanate reign.[1][2] It was part of Siri, the second medieval city of India of the Delhi Sultanate of Alauddin Khalji Dynasty (1296–1316).[1][2] The etymology of the name Hauz Khas in Persian is derived from the words ‘Hauz’: \"water tank\" (or lake) and ‘Khas’:\"royal\"- the \"Royal tank\". The large water tank or reservoir was first built by Allauddin Khilji (the plaque displayed at the site records this fact) to supply water to the inhabitants of Siri.[3] The tank was de–silted during the reign of Firuz Shah Tughlaq (1351–88). Several buildings (Mosque and madrasa) and tombs were built overlooking the water tank or lake. Firuz Shah\'s tomb pivots the L–shaped building complex which overlooks the tank.</string>
    <string name="snajayvan_description">Sanjay Van is a sprawling city forest area near Vasant Kunj and Mehrauli in Delhi, India. It is spread over an area of 443 acres. It is one of the most thickly wooded areas of the city’s green lungs.\n</string>
    <string name="lodhi_garden_description">odi Gardens is a city park situated in New Delhi, India. Spread over 90 acres (360,000 m2),[1] it contains Mohammed Shah\'s Tomb, the Tomb of Sikandar Lodi, the Shisha Gumbad and the Bara Gumbad,[2] architectural works of the 15th century by Lodis - who ruled parts of northern India and Punjab and Khyber Pakhtunkhwa province of modern-day Pakistan, from 1451 to 1526. The site is now protected by the Archaeological Survey of India (ASI).[1]\n\n\nLodhi Gardens is popular for exercise and walking enthusiasts\nThe gardens are situated between Khan Market and Safdarjung\'s Tomb on Lodi Road and is a popular spot for morning walks for the Delhites.</string>
    <string name="mughal_garden_description">Mughal Gardens are a type of garden built by the Mughals. This style was influenced by the Persian gardens particularly the Charbagh structure,[1] which is intended to create a representation of an earthly utopia in which humans co-exist in perfect harmony with all elements of nature.\n\nSignificant use of rectilinear layouts are made within the walls enclosures. Some of the typical features include pools, fountains and canals inside the gardens. Afghanistan, Bangladesh and India have a number of gardens which differ from their Central Asian predecessors with respect to \"the highly disciplined geometry\"</string>
    <string name="akshardham_temple_description">Swaminarayan Akshardham is a Hindu temple and spiritual-cultural campus in Delhi, India. The temple is close to the border with Noida. Also referred to as Akshardham Temple or Akshardham Delhi, the complex displays millennia of traditional and modern Hindu culture, spirituality, and architecture. Inspired by Yogiji Maharaj and created by Pramukh Swami Maharaj, it was constructed by BAPS.[2] It is the world\'s second-largest BAPS Hindu temple, following Akshardham, New Jersey, in the United States.</string>
    <string name="lotus_temple_description">The Lotus Temple, located in New Delhi, India, is a Baháʼí House of Worship that was dedicated in December 1986. Notable for its lotus-like shape, it has become a prominent attraction in the city. Like all Bahá’í Houses of Worship, the Lotus Temple is open to all, regardless of religion or any other qualification. The building is composed of 27 free-standing marble-clad \"petals\" arranged in clusters of three to form nine sides,[1] with nine doors opening onto a central hall with a height of slightly over 34 metres[1] and a capacity of 1,300 people.[2] The Lotus Temple has won numerous architectural awards[3][4] and has been featured in many newspaper and magazine articles.</string>
    <string name="isckon_temple_description">Sri Sri Radha Parthasarathi Mandir, generally known as the ISKCON Delhi temple, is a well known Vaishnav temple of Krishna and Radha in the form of Radha Parthasarathi. The Temple was inaugurated on 5 April, 1998 by the then Prime Minister of India, Atal Bihari Vajpayee[1] in the presence of former Chief Minister of Delhi, Sahib Singh Verma, and Sushma Swaraj. It is located at Hare Krishna Hills (near Nehru Place), in the East of Kailash area of New Delhi, India.</string>

</resources>